<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Knights on Morgana&#39;s Watchtower Notes</title>
    <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/tags/knights/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Knights on Morgana&#39;s Watchtower Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:38:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/tags/knights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Name&#39;s Simon Bastil and I&#39;m Here to Rescue You</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:38:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-21/</guid>
      <description>Emergency Alert! The fuck did you guys do on Wednesday? Tilda Swinton is not doing great, kind of on a descent and MacIntyre+Orlaith are turning against her Cleric Orlaith is here, councillor We got outplayed by Hemlock, probably a spy Creel kidnapped in previous session Larry is the one assigning Enigma to babysitting duty. Keeping her out of the way??? Location 4 stories, including a basement We need to get in, and get out with Creel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley Knights</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-14/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-14 Fri&amp;gt;Death Valley Knights Lord Commander MacIntyre meeting: Internal security (Time MI5) Florence Scarred Man: Stole ChronoCo stuff from the tower and fled. Unaffiliated or SecondHand Salamas Scarred Man: Hemlock. Goals: Find out where the information went, how it was stolen. Learn about the men and where they came from. Salamas Guy Was being interrogated by Clinton Good Cop Bad Cop Lightning Gun : Standard High Tech Eight step plan of world domination First step: Trickery, done Second step has happened now.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
