<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Morgana&#39;s Watchtower Notes</title>
    <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Morgana&#39;s Watchtower Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://vivianwilde.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley Knights</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/posts/06-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/posts/06-14/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-14 Fri&amp;gt;Death Valley Knights Lord Commander MacIntyre meeting: Internal security (Time MI5) Stolen intel: 36 hours unaccounted for, enough time for the code to have been decrypted. Could be Hemlock. Florence Scarred Man: Stole ChronoCo stuff from the tower and fled. Unaffiliated or SecondHand Salamas Scarred Man: Hemlock. Goals: Find out where the information went, how it was stolen. Learn about the men and where they came from. Stolen again somewhere between Florence and Italy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tasha&#39;s Estate</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/posts/06-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/posts/06-09/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-09 Sun&amp;gt;Ace Squad Timeline (new entries) 9:30-12: Council Meeting 12:30: Tasha visited Alec ~12:30: Tasha got a text from Alex saying &amp;#34;I&amp;#39;ll kill you if you tell anyone about this&amp;#34;, but previous messages are very chill. So text might be a ruse??? 1:30: Tasha working at the union office 3:30 Emergency Meeting: Tasha, Clinton, Doe, Tuhorn, and a full list of others were late and the Lone Master sent a rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Greece</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/posts/06-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/posts/06-02/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-02 Sun&amp;gt;First Session Let&amp;#39;s Fucking Go! Receptacle Adel Boiss - Persian Spy W: +3 A: +4 T: +2 C:+2 H:+0 Ability - Persian Connections: The Persians, an opposing military force, trust Boiss&amp;#39;s decrees…&#xA;Case Temporal anomaly - symptoms of sickness, etc.&#xA;NPC: Selene Assistant to Madame E, Watcher We&amp;#39;ve worked together, casually.&#xA;Notes A thief escaped and disappeared into the timestream, stole a list of some sensitive info Time Exits: One, presumably a thief Exit to ancient greece around 500BC, caused a ripple leading to a break in 480.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
