<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Morgana&#39;s Case Notes</title>
    <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Morgana&#39;s Case Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:23:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Holly Holland&#39;s Minecraft Game</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:23:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-23/</guid>
      <description>TIFU by Letting my Bestie Trusted Colleague Get Captured By a Capitalist [CENSORED] Notes on the basement walls Several inconsistencies 21 days: &amp;#34;The End?&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;TIMEOUT&amp;#34;, NOTE: &amp;#34;The end&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;worried about the franchise&amp;#34; was in the book club “What do they want” Chrono: Holly TL -&amp;gt; Power Knight: End of HEMLOCK Watcher: Our fail -&amp;gt; End of us SH: Stop the end HEMLOCK: Fight the Fight TIMEOUT: The End of Everything Oh, timeout, those mysterious guys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Name&#39;s Simon Bastil and I&#39;m Here to Rescue You</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:38:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-21/</guid>
      <description>Emergency Alert! The fuck did you guys do on Wednesday? Tilda Swinton is not doing great, kind of on a descent and MacIntyre+Orlaith are turning against her Cleric Orlaith is here, councillor We got outplayed by Hemlock, probably a spy Creel kidnapped in previous session Enigma&amp;#39;s Watcher councillor is the one assigning her to babysitting duty.&#xA;Location 4 stories, including a basement We need to get in, and get out with Creel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Chimpanzee, A Hologram, and A Magpie Walk Into A Bar...</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-16/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-16 Sun&amp;gt;A Chimpanzee, A Hologram, and A Magpie Walk Into A Bar… Breacher Found the keys to Tasha&amp;#39;s code Last Resort: Place in Tahoe Running for the council, as is Mr Time. Book club: Mildred, Benny, Tasha, Cousin Riley Didn&amp;#39;t find the journal, interesting Dr Rain Jake Robertson Political opinions &amp;#34;Making a change&amp;#34; &amp;#34;I guess that&amp;#39;s what happens to you after you get a PhD and realize it wasn&amp;#39;t worth anything…&amp;#34; Zephyr Convo Jake: Sent by Lightborn (ChronoCo) or Tuhorn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley Knights</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-14/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-14 Fri&amp;gt;Death Valley Knights Lord Commander MacIntyre meeting: Internal security (Time MI5) Florence Scarred Man: Stole ChronoCo stuff from the tower and fled. Unaffiliated or SecondHand Salamas Scarred Man: Hemlock. Goals: Find out where the information went, how it was stolen. Learn about the men and where they came from. Salamas Guy Was being interrogated by Clinton Good Cop Bad Cop Lightning Gun : Standard High Tech Eight step plan of world domination First step: Trickery, done Second step has happened now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tasha&#39;s Estate</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-09/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-09 Sun&amp;gt;Ace Squad Timeline (new entries) 9:30-12: Council Meeting 12:30: Tasha visited Alec ~12:30: Tasha got a text from Alex saying &amp;#34;I&amp;#39;ll kill you if you tell anyone about this&amp;#34;, but previous messages are very chill. So text might be a ruse??? 1:30: Tasha working at the union office 3:30 Emergency Meeting: Tasha, Clinton, Doe, Tuhorn, and a full list of others were late and the Lone Master sent a rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Murder of Tasha Tennyson</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-07/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-07 Fri&amp;gt; The Murder of Tasha Tennyson Notes taken and published from the case files of Enigma, my respected colleague in Watchery, mystery-solving, and sharpshooting.&#xA;The Heist Theft Confidential information was stolen from the Watchtower, prompting all factions to scurry in a race to retrieve it before anything got leaked; though we are working together, all factions have their own agendas… It is suspected that an unknown scarred man was behind the theft and is related to the shooting of Tasha Tennyson Watchtower Shooting Background Minutemen faction leader and Councilor Tasha Tennyson was murdered while most of us were off on our missions, supposedly by Watcher Inspector Seline (who is M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek Life (The Piratical Kind)</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/posts/06-02/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-02 Sun&amp;gt;First Session Let&amp;#39;s Fucking Go! Receptacle Adel Boiss - Persian Spy W: +3 A: +4 T: +2 C:+2 H:+0 Ability - Persian Connections: The Persians, an opposing military force, trust Boiss&amp;#39;s decrees…&#xA;Case Temporal anomaly - symptoms of sickness, etc.&#xA;NPC: Selene Assistant to Madame E, Watcher We&amp;#39;ve worked together, casually.&#xA;Notes A thief escaped and disappeared into the timestream, stole a list of some sensitive info Time Exits: One, presumably a thief Exit to ancient greece around 500BC, caused a ripple leading to a break in 480.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
