<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Morgana&#39;s Case Notes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Morgana&#39;s Case Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Radiant Dawn</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-21/</guid>
      <description>Session Watchers at the throat of the minutemen Thorwald is also anti-minutemen, on the same side as the whisperer Watcher and ChronoCo: There&amp;#39;s a lot, but we don&amp;#39;t know the details ChronoCo vs knights: Dr. Lightborn is anti-knight, no fighting yet. So we can convince knights that Holly was unsanctioned Convince chronoCo that the bullshit was Larry Pitch Meeting TIME has a paradox in his head, but seems under control Cecilia hugged Rosemary!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkest Hour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-19/</guid>
      <description>ChronoCo Everything is in disarray Terrorist Scum! Grasshopper is dead Enigma, Nic, and Magpie, and the Daltons, are here. Simon is also here! Conversations Cecilia&amp;#39;s on our side - not secondhand, but willing to convince Will to stop the apocalypse. We need to convince Will on Sunday We showed Cecilia the apocalypse Breakout Watch them on the cameras, try to suss out weaknesses and hidden tricks via Juniper BS Riley and Rosemary will scream abuse through the intercoms Blast doors: try to isolate Larry Jane&amp;#39;s masks exist So assume Marlow is there ready to neutralise any teleports we apply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Family Ball</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-17/</guid>
      <description>Planning If we kill Larry Blame ChronoCo and go to war Blame the Secondhand, bipartisan nuke us for councillor-killing and then cheer squad does cheer squad things How do we State of play Marlow wants to kill Larry Enigma also seems to Phoenix, Izzy and I are hoping to incriminate him rather than kill, and protect whoever Larry is targeting. Costume Full AC Eh, not really AC/Juniper Mask: Golden/yellow light around the eyeholes, polished metal all around and bronze gear and circuit designs (including a large gear on the side as the &amp;#34;accessory&amp;#34;) (camera and sensor/scanner capabilities) A facemask that looks like a grille/speaker (audio recording, optionally communicating with the group) Metallic-grey robes with accents in ChronoCo gold and knightly red trimmings A little commemorative Velociraptor pin from Dinosaur Park Ace pride pins because puns A little handcuff keychain hanging from a belt loop The Game Dalton has anti-hologram tech Tell Sam: I forgot to say this because I was talking with Miri, but Juniper would&amp;#39;ve gotten there a little early to search for camera and security system blind spots Larry Threads have blue traces pointing to where they are Jane Doe&amp;#39;s entry She has someone new by her side Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anyway, I Believe You Were Tracking a Snail Using Narcotics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-14/</guid>
      <description>Hello Juniper Spaceship is a trap. &amp;#34;Ship shall be the Second&amp;#39;s grave&amp;#34; We got pocketwatches from Dalton 15 trips to take stuff to the SecondHand Breacher is Frida Aleman because of course she fucking is She did some receptacle bullshit We accidentally built the same characters Snail Snail&amp;#39;s shell structure is spiraled/structured chronite. It blips between timelines and eras, but is still very stable Carboniferous era Bullet hole in the trees Some kind of rifle, futuristic (so 2100 or later, thereabouts) Something large has been dragged along the floor to the west Some sort of armored arthropod has been dragged: A big centipede according to Phoenix Last person here: Fired a gun shot, steampunk pith helmet, shot a centipede and dragged it off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cause of Death: Fucking With the Watchers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/fanfic/my_death/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/fanfic/my_death/</guid>
      <description>As Jane taps her stick against the ground, Morgana whispers a curse under her breath, and prepares to reach new heights of stupidity - willingly drawing the attention of the walking nightmare named Jane Doe. She settles on her favorite kind of distraction - a bullet fired straight for Jane&amp;#39;s trademark swordstick.&#xA;It misses, of course. But it does its job, as Jane looks away from the stabiliser and whips around to chase them down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knight Falls On Dutch Shores</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-12/</guid>
      <description>Simon&amp;#39;s Presentation Florence Simon reacted Gnomeo and Juliet in Florence Objectives Kill Holly Holland Hold/Take the Stabilizer Transport Time Fluid through the Refinery Actual Game Holly&amp;#39;s at war, threatened to blow up the moon Minuteman are screwed, Breacher and Wilde are dead Automatons decommissioned but the knights want the last few for the war against Holland We want to fight our way to Holly&amp;#39;s timeline room Then find which Timeline she&amp;#39;s in Then take control of the time stabilizer Chronite: Large amounts of it dilates time, but volatile and can do temporal damage if pressurised/etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let Me Know If You See Any Good Cows</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-07/</guid>
      <description>Paradox Banished to the Time Mines in Mr TIME&amp;#39;s mind Rosemary is traumatised now Engineer Timeline Desert vibes Like in the video A castle on a hill Medieval-style houses Giant mound of some strange dirt and skeletons &amp;#34;The mayor&amp;#34; opening up that place after so long &amp;#34;Should be nice for us to visit&amp;#34; Two manequins with outfits There&amp;#39;s some purple, and purple was rare in normal medieval times. Mayor&amp;#39;s shindig in the castle: Wear something fancy Unscrupulous devil-worshippers The devil was here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goblin I guess</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-05/</guid>
      <description> The Goblin A green power ranger Grasshopper We&amp;#39;re on a timeline, every second counts Enigma&amp;#39;s in-person, rest of us are receptacling Enigma&amp;#39;s pocketwatch will bring them back. &amp;#34;Something is weird about Enigma&amp;#34; she&amp;#39;ll be fine Jett found out about Madame E Marlow is doing mystery stuff in a channel Breacher is under investigation from Jane Doe We destroyed another timeline Wilde has a daughter We killed AC it was a mess </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watcher Headquarters</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/07-03/</guid>
      <description>Raise Your Glass High For Tomorrow We Die False pretenses We&amp;#39;re both here Jane Doe drugged Leonardo DaVinci Jane Doe has a cane. She tends to have one a lot, it&amp;#39;s one of her tells Person in a trench coat took Enigma&amp;#39;s watch. Presumably to add Watcher spyware Video: Questioning To Enigma: &amp;#34;Where were you in the mines?&amp;#34; Enigma: &amp;#34;Someone from somewhere who could change and destroy everything&amp;#34; Enigma was supposed to be dead, I don&amp;#39;t like this new Enigma as much as the old We needed an Enigma to die in the mines to start the whole thing off, but you didn&amp;#39;t die.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Am I Gonna Be An Optimist About This?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 11:32:35 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-30/</guid>
      <description>Cat Convo Not a receptacle Saw Selene slightly before she last saw Tasha Selene ran downstairs, below the house. 8-9 sleeps ago. So when the 21 days dates from So around the deathday Tasha wrote &amp;#34;21 days&amp;#34; close to the time of her death 21 days could be a calendar. Cat: Does not remember seeing Malcolm Went down to the basement, got placed on a disk and got a little bit woozy, and then no memories after that Then being taken off the disc, and Tasha comes down, pops out a tube and gets worried and writing stuff and putting up the So some of the post-its came after Selene and cat visited the resort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No to Communism, Yes to Communes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-28/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-28 Fri&amp;gt;Knights Game In the CTE We saw an illusory image of myself, tracking time fluid with the magpie back in Greece. What does this mean? Is it related to the AC paradox? Is something coming back around? Was it a warning to be aware of time fluid? &amp;#34;Nicolas Aurora&amp;#34; Santa Claus Nicolas Aurora May or may not be in Watcher personnel files Gave me an unlit cartoon bomb Apparently current Saint Nick is his successor Marlow Is he the Lone Master&amp;#39;s?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving Enigma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:13:35 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-26/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-26 Wed&amp;gt; Convo Hannaly is doing better than we thought So is Breacher! Mine incident: Dalton describes it as &amp;#34;interesting&amp;#34;, and seems vaguely concerned. Holly: &amp;#34;Show that she&amp;#39;s unharmed&amp;#34; Enigma &amp;#34;As long as there&amp;#39;s a fight hemlock will be there.&amp;#34; Or something to that effect Clown &amp;lt;2024-06-27 Thu&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Stuff happens&amp;gt; Clown remembers vague memories about being a child here, watching blorbo and then waking up in a grave The memories of Malachai seem to be missing Blorbo spawns, blorbo knows we&amp;#39;ll follow it There&amp;#39;s a doctor in the chair in room 666 Don&amp;#39;t worry watchers, it&amp;#39;ll be consistent but also inconsistent, isn&amp;#39;t that great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuhorn</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/tuhorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/tuhorn/</guid>
      <description>Tuhorn Convo &amp;lt;2024-06-24 Mon&amp;gt; Tuhorn has a secret hobbit hole in providence park Who sent the invite: &amp;#34;Dearest friend and your friend too, [points at breacher] she was perhaps but one of two&amp;#34; What was he doing: &amp;#34;Scanning, looking far, trying to end the war&amp;#34; &amp;#34;Perhaps I need a lift&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Watcher might work, but sometimes they don&amp;#39;t when they&amp;#39;re ruled by a jerk&amp;#34;. All of them are jerks Madame E: Jerk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Holly Holland&#39;s Minecraft Game</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:23:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-23/</guid>
      <description>TIFU by Letting my Bestie Trusted Colleague Get Captured By a Capitalist [BLEEP] Notes on the basement walls Several inconsistencies 21 days: &amp;#34;The End?&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;TIMEOUT&amp;#34;, NOTE: &amp;#34;The end&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;worried about the franchise&amp;#34; was in the book club “What do they want” Chrono: Holly TL -&amp;gt; Power Knight: End of HEMLOCK Watcher: Our fail -&amp;gt; End of us SH: Stop the end HEMLOCK: Fight the Fight TIMEOUT: The End of Everything Oh, timeout, those mysterious guys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/debates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 23:04:15 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/debates/</guid>
      <description>First time I&amp;#39;m hearing the clown&amp;#39;s voice. Exciting. Good to put a voice to the name What&amp;#39;s Breacher up to? Three seats. Interesting Shoutout to everyone&amp;#39;s improv abilities, you all are good at this &amp;#34;Mysteriously British Watcher&amp;#34; was referenced at some point, and Marlow&amp;#39;s speech is so British. &amp;#34;Scuffle&amp;#34;. Marlow: Hawkish but sane. Why is the clown making sense? I don&amp;#39;t like this. Damien: &amp;#34;At least two&amp;#34; councillors removed. That&amp;#39;s a choice of words, what do you know?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Call it Paradise, I Don&#39;t Know Why</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/last-resort/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/last-resort/</guid>
      <description>Enigma isn&amp;#39;t with us. Sadness. I&amp;#39;m sorry!&#xA;COMMENT Breacher Updates Tilda Clinton got erased from the timeline???? Oh. That&amp;#39;s why Rachel Anderson was there with the androids rather than AC erased Clinton, and he&amp;#39;s secretly working for Rachel Anderson Oh. Fuck. Last Resort Buildings are pristine but decaying Used to be &amp;#34;laguna/lagoon (?) resort and spa&amp;#34;, now &amp;#34;last resort and spa&amp;#34; It&amp;#39;s our-timeline Lake Tahoe, around 2430 So around 30 years into the future Rooms Reheated frozen meal A few branching off hallways - Suites Pool, Lake access, Sauna, Spa Sauna and pool: Generic but nice COMMENT Lake There&amp;#39;s a figure with white robes skipping stones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Name&#39;s Simon Bastil and I&#39;m Here to Rescue You</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:38:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-21/</guid>
      <description>Emergency Alert! The fuck did you guys do on Wednesday? Tilda Swinton is not doing great, kind of on a descent and MacIntyre+Orlaith are turning against her Cleric Orlaith is here, councillor We got outplayed by Hemlock, probably a spy Creel kidnapped in previous session Enigma&amp;#39;s Watcher councillor is the one assigning her to babysitting duty.&#xA;Location 4 stories, including a basement We need to get in, and get out with Creel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Chimpanzee, A Hologram, and A Magpie Walk Into A Bar...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-16/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-16 Sun&amp;gt;A Chimpanzee, A Hologram, and A Magpie Walk Into A Bar… Breacher Found the keys to Tasha&amp;#39;s code Last Resort: Place in Tahoe Running for the council, as is Mr Time. Book club: Mildred, Benny, Tasha, Cousin Riley Didn&amp;#39;t find the journal, interesting Dr Rain Jake Robertson Political opinions &amp;#34;Making a change&amp;#34; &amp;#34;I guess that&amp;#39;s what happens to you after you get a PhD and realize it wasn&amp;#39;t worth anything…&amp;#34; Zephyr Convo Jake: Sent by Lightborn (ChronoCo) or Tuhorn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley Knights</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-14/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-14 Fri&amp;gt;Death Valley Knights Lord Commander MacIntyre meeting: Internal security (Time MI5) Florence Scarred Man: Stole ChronoCo stuff from the tower and fled. Unaffiliated or SecondHand Salamas Scarred Man: Hemlock. Goals: Find out where the information went, how it was stolen. Learn about the men and where they came from. Salamas Guy Was being interrogated by Clinton Good Cop Bad Cop Lightning Gun : Standard High Tech Eight step plan of world domination First step: Trickery, done Second step has happened now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tasha&#39;s Estate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-09/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-09 Sun&amp;gt;Ace Squad Timeline (new entries) 9:30-12: Council Meeting 12:30: Tasha visited Alec ~12:30: Tasha got a text from Alex saying &amp;#34;I&amp;#39;ll kill you if you tell anyone about this&amp;#34;, but previous messages are very chill. So text might be a ruse??? 1:30: Tasha working at the union office 3:30 Emergency Meeting: Tasha, Clinton, Doe, Tuhorn, and a full list of others were late and the Lone Master sent a rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Murder of Tasha Tennyson</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-07/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-07 Fri&amp;gt; The Murder of Tasha Tennyson Notes taken and published from the case files of Enigma, my respected colleague in Watchery, mystery-solving, and sharpshooting.&#xA;The Heist Theft Confidential information was stolen from the Watchtower, prompting all factions to scurry in a race to retrieve it before anything got leaked; though we are working together, all factions have their own agendas… It is suspected that an unknown scarred man was behind the theft and is related to the shooting of Tasha Tennyson Watchtower Shooting Background Minutemen faction leader and Councilor Tasha Tennyson was murdered while most of us were off on our missions, supposedly by Watcher Inspector Seline (who is M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek Life (The Piratical Kind)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/06-02/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;2024-06-02 Sun&amp;gt;First Session Let&amp;#39;s Fucking Go! Receptacle Adel Boiss - Persian Spy W: +3 A: +4 T: +2 C:+2 H:+0 Ability - Persian Connections: The Persians, an opposing military force, trust Boiss&amp;#39;s decrees…&#xA;Case Temporal anomaly - symptoms of sickness, etc.&#xA;NPC: Selene Assistant to Madame E, Watcher We&amp;#39;ve worked together, casually.&#xA;Notes A thief escaped and disappeared into the timestream, stole a list of some sensitive info Time Exits: One, presumably a thief Exit to ancient greece around 500BC, caused a ripple leading to a break in 480.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/enigma_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/enigma_notes/</guid>
      <description>THE WATCHTOWER WATCHTOWER INFO https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1hpHTmiOTQEcQ4buwW32vU7zOE-B3lJIesMhNP6n0aOM/edit#slide=id.p Worldbuilding Lore/Technical Info (READ THIS) https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/13ueGPhZb8ikg10uMSkF0qoe-03QeuVYaRa2AbyILB-o/edit#slide=id.p NPC List https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1FuLZwgKKDVrBMxvuKgB7dBbhxqgVw8k-Cs34pNlGth4/edit?usp=sharing&#xA;Members: The Council (Sam) Knights: Damien Beowulf Trayr (Anu); Simon Bastil (Jandro); AC-001X (Manav); Phoenix (Bryce) Watchers: Marlow MacPherson (Ryan); Miri (Nikita); Morgan Ilkay (Vivien); Brad (Sabrina); Sidney Stockton (Soup); Nicholas Aurora/The Eyes Unseen (Manav); Juniper Snow (Vivien) Chrono-Co: R.R. Hurlabur (Ben, brother of Sam); Mr. Time (Andrew); The Clown (Nate); Rosemary (Nila); Jungwon Moon (Jun) Minutemen: Jett (Aryan); Anastasia &amp;ldquo;Breacher&amp;rdquo; Dustin (Bryce); Ross Perot (Aryan); The Magpie (Jasmine); Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheer Squad Dossier</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/larry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/larry/</guid>
      <description>Jane Deadly with a sword cane: x3 attacks, 2d6+6 each +6 agility and hardiness, insane character, insane-r wis, ?? tech but does that even matter? Ability to “smite” people back to their original era, including Watchtower agents. Ability to slow others down in order to speed herself up. So a &amp;ldquo;haste&amp;rdquo; ability of unknown scale, this is worrying. Quite likely has a hopwatch and so weak to temporal (Hat-tip to Phoenix for this one) Larry Known General Rarely takes the field, but deadly when he does If he&amp;rsquo;s not a field agent, hopefully has low Hardiness and Agility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes Unseen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/case_notes/eyes/</guid>
      <description> Watcher Councillor Watchers are keeping an eye on &amp;#34;Certain info on what the councillors are doing&amp;#34; Vested interest in Enigma Preventing apocalypse Why they know: Have eyes everywhere Larry: What do I know about the nature of his strings Do the threads have something to do with Enigma being an anomaly. Eyes knows stuff about Enigma. &amp;#34;Certainly is&amp;#34;, in response to the &amp;#39;destroy and change everything&amp;#39; If we can get Madame E that would help &amp;#34;Not at liberty to say&amp;#34; if Madame E We need to find out where Madame E is She might be trapped </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Lieu Of An Epilogue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/fanfic/more_time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/fanfic/more_time/</guid>
      <description>2d12+1 Things Morgana Would&amp;rsquo;ve Done If She Had More Time Forgiven Enigma immediately and bought her ice cream as a welcome back present Introduced Enigma to MCR and black eyeliner Super-soaker duels with Enigma - they had a whole plan to call it &amp;ldquo;sparring practice&amp;rdquo; to get her to agree Help Enigma break Brad out of prison before Marlow could execute him Helped break Tuhorn out of prison, and then given him a long rambling apology from within the silence field (she forgot it was on) Stabbed all of Larry Morton&amp;rsquo;s limbs with needles coated in neurotoxin Constantly texted Enigma little jokes during council meetings until she muted her notifications Rock-paper-scissors with Breacher for who gets to walk Enigma down the aisle at her wedding Genuinely cried when Enigma Luna Ilkay announced her new name Mourned Breacher properly Chewed out Breacher for faking her death and not letting them know Taking advantage of Breacher having an actual body to give her a surprise hug Begged Breacher to repurpose one of her hologram projectors for a movie night Sent Cecilia Dalton an anonymous email containing a full essay on why Rosemary is the coolest Challenged Phantom of the Disco to a duel and probably shot him Time-travelled to a Girl In Red concert with Rosemary Taken the entire group (bloodhounds,ace squad,Izzy) on a trip to Lake Tahoe before it became an irradiated hellscape, just so they could enjoy it together Shooting practice with Magpie, Miri&amp;rsquo;s kaleidoscope, and a nerf gun Swapped out Simon&amp;rsquo;s alcohol stash with soda, and then faked her death and gone into hiding Tricked Miri into coming to a Jeremies concert Finally taken Paladin Tracker up on his offer of a Die Hard Marathon Disappeared into the Watcher Archive for weeks on end with Sidney and emerged with encyclopedic knowledge of every ornithopter prison escapes and no memory of what they went in there for (this would be a regular occurence) Borrowed Phoenix&amp;rsquo;s panspectrals to play hide-and-seek with Magpie Played puzzle games with Miri and gotten really competitive about it Told all of you how much you meant to her </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magpie&#39;s Epilogue: Addendum</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/fanfic/luna_magpie_snippet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchtower-blog/posts/fanfic/luna_magpie_snippet/</guid>
      <description>Luna&amp;rsquo;s not even surprised when she walks into her office and sees Magpie rooting through her drawers, desperately looking for trinkets to pawn. They&amp;rsquo;ve worked out a tacit arrangement where Magpie never takes anything too important, and she&amp;rsquo;ll usually steal it back if Luna promises enough credits (Magpie gives Luna the &amp;lsquo;friends and family&amp;rsquo; 0.1% discount. It&amp;rsquo;s her own little way of showing she cares)&#xA;&amp;ldquo;No Magpie, I don&amp;rsquo;t have any credits&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
