<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fanfics on Morgana&#39;s Case Notes</title>
    <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fanfics on Morgana&#39;s Case Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cause of Death: Fucking With the Watchers</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/my_death/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/my_death/</guid>
      <description>As Jane taps her stick against the ground, Morgana whispers a curse under her breath, and prepares to reach new heights of stupidity - willingly drawing the attention of the walking nightmare named Jane Doe. She settles on her favorite kind of distraction - a bullet fired straight for Jane&amp;#39;s trademark swordstick.&#xA;It misses, of course. But it does its job, as Jane looks away from the stabiliser and whips around to chase them down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/last_goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/last_goodbye/</guid>
      <description>Last Goodbye Enigma catches Morgana before they can slip away to destroy the destabilisers, and tries to dissuade them. It doesn’t change anything.&#xA;For the sake of clarity, I’m just going to consistently use they/them for Morgana and she/her for Enigma so that we don’t have to wrangle referents of pronouns&#xA;I will be doing over-the-top amounts of angst, I apologise&#xA;Morgana Simon laughs as he waves his robot arm (and not-quite robot-hand) at Morgana and shouts “Reattached limb buddies!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/memories/</guid>
      <description>Memories in the cold-case I amped cold-case so that it conveys subjective impressions as well as just events. This is most certainly not a copout so that I can avoid having to follow the &amp;ldquo;show, don&amp;rsquo;t tell&amp;rdquo; maxim. Canonically, the thing that decided Morgana&amp;rsquo;s break from the watchers was her imagining Miri dying as an 18 year old and swearing that she&amp;rsquo;d die rather than stand by and let that happen (and die she did)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold Case Memories - Enigma</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/enigma_memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/enigma_memories/</guid>
      <description>Morgana and Enigma talking to Zephyr together and coordinating with little looks and whispers, agreeing almost instinctively on what pressure to put and what secrets we can safely share… and then swapping identical looks of frustration as Simon throws all that to the winds and starts telling the story.&#xA;—&#xA;Creeping through a Hemlock base, Morgana sees Enigma get downed while rushing to the computer. A burst of protectiveness comes over them, and they send a bolt of lightning arcing towards whoever shot her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Lieu Of An Epilogue</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/more_time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/more_time/</guid>
      <description>2d12+1 Things Morgana Would&amp;rsquo;ve Done If She Had More Time Forgiven Enigma immediately and bought her ice cream as a welcome back present Introduced Enigma to MCR and black eyeliner Super-soaker duels with Enigma - they had a whole plan to call it &amp;ldquo;sparring practice&amp;rdquo; to get her to agree Help Enigma break Brad out of prison before Marlow could execute him Helped break Tuhorn out of prison, and then given him a long rambling apology from within the silence field (she forgot it was on) Stabbed all of Larry Morton&amp;rsquo;s limbs with needles coated in neurotoxin Constantly texted Enigma little jokes during council meetings until she muted her notifications Rock-paper-scissors with Breacher for who gets to walk Enigma down the aisle at her wedding Genuinely cried when Enigma Luna Ilkay announced her new name Mourned Breacher properly Chewed out Breacher for faking her death and not letting them know Taking advantage of Breacher having an actual body to give her a surprise hug Begged Breacher to repurpose one of her hologram projectors for a movie night Sent Cecilia Dalton an anonymous email containing a full essay on why Rosemary is the coolest Challenged Phantom of the Disco to a duel and probably shot him Time-travelled to a Girl In Red concert with Rosemary Taken the entire group (bloodhounds,ace squad,Izzy) on a trip to Lake Tahoe before it became an irradiated hellscape, just so they could enjoy it together Shooting practice with Magpie, Miri&amp;rsquo;s kaleidoscope, and a nerf gun Swapped out Simon&amp;rsquo;s alcohol stash with soda, and then faked her death and gone into hiding Tricked Miri into coming to a Jeremies concert Finally taken Paladin Tracker up on his offer of a Die Hard Marathon Disappeared into the Watcher Archive for weeks on end with Sidney and emerged with encyclopedic knowledge of every ornithopter prison escapes and no memory of what they went in there for (this would be a regular occurence) Borrowed Phoenix&amp;rsquo;s panspectrals to play hide-and-seek with Magpie Played puzzle games with Miri and gotten really competitive about it Told all of you how much you meant to her </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magpie&#39;s Epilogue: Addendum</title>
      <link>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/luna_magpie_snippet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vivianwilde.github.io/watchtower-blog/fanfic/luna_magpie_snippet/</guid>
      <description>Luna&amp;rsquo;s not even surprised when she walks into her office and sees Magpie rooting through her drawers, desperately looking for trinkets to pawn. They&amp;rsquo;ve worked out a tacit arrangement where Magpie never takes anything too important, and she&amp;rsquo;ll usually steal it back if Luna promises enough credits (Magpie gives Luna the &amp;lsquo;friends and family&amp;rsquo; 0.1% discount. It&amp;rsquo;s her own little way of showing she cares)&#xA;&amp;ldquo;No Magpie, I don&amp;rsquo;t have any credits&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
